Guide to the Bronislaw Malinowski Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1869-1939; Series I
  - Correspondence of Bronislaw Malinowski
    - Bousios, Basil N. H., 1936 October 14, November 5 (Box 1, Folder 71, Reel 1)
    - Bowman, Isaiah, President of Johns Hopkins University, 1936 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 72, Reel 1)
    - Bridgeman, _____, 1932 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 73, Reel 1)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1930, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 74, Reel 1)
    - British Film Institute; J. W. Brown, 1934 March 26, April 6 (Box 1, Folder 75, Reel 1)
    - British Institute of Philosophy; Sidney E. Hooper, 1931, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 76, Reel 1)
    - British Library of Political and Economic Science
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 621
    - British Population Society; Eldon Moore, Mabel C. Buer, 1931, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 77, Reel 1)
    - British Psychological Society, 1933 December 5, December 9 (Box 1, Folder 78, Reel 1)
    - British Social Hygiene Council; E. O. Grant, F. Blackett, 1930-1933 (Box 1, Folder 79, Reel 1)
    - Curtis Brown, Ltd., 1933 November 8 (Box 1, Folder 80, Reel 1)
    - Brown, George Gordon and Elizabeth, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 81, Reel 1)
    - Brownlee, Frank, 1931 August 24 (Box 1, Folder 82, Reel 1)
    - Brudo, Raphael, 1925-1938, undated (Box 1, Folder 83 - 84, Reel 1)
    - Brunton Annie, 1916, 1934-1938 (Box 1, Folder 85, Reel 1)
    - Brzeziński, Stanisław, 1933-1938 (Box 1, Folder 86, Reel 1)
    - Buck, Pearl S., 1933 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 87, Reel 1)
    - Buck, Peter H., 1935 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 88, Reel 1)
    - Buckby, Charles W., 1932 October 14 (Box 1, Folder 89, Reel 1)
    - Buer, Mabel C.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 77
    - Bujak, Fr[anciszek?], 1928 December 28, 1930 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 90, Reel 1)
    - Bunl, Bertha and Hans, 1936 July 11 (Box 2, Folder 91, Reel 1)
    - Burns, Cecil Delisle, n.y. January 23 (Box 2, Folder 92, Reel 1)
    - Busch, Hans, 1932 August 28, September 9 (Box 2, Folder 93, Reel 1)
    - Butchart, Montgomery
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 663
    - Byrne, Father Joseph, 1935 August 16 (Box 2, Folder 94, Reel 1)
    - Cabot, P. S., 1936 September 16, November 8 (Box 2, Folder 95, Reel 1)
    - Cairns, Huntington, 1935 June 11, June 24 (Box 2, Folder 96, Reel 1)
    - Campbell, J., Acting Assistant Resident Magistrate, Losuia, S.E.D., 1915 August 23, October 4 (Box 2, Folder 97, Reel 1)
    - Campkin, Dennis, 1932 March 1, April 29 (Box 2, Folder 98, Reel 1)
    - Capelle, W., 1936 October 8 (Box 2, Folder 99, Reel 1)
    - Carnegie Corporation; Frederick P. Keppel, 1934 February 1, May 17 (Box 2, Folder 100, Reel 1)
    - Carpenter, C. R., 1936 October 7, November 5 (Box 2, Folder 101, Reel 1)
    - Carpenter, Niles, 1935 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 102, Reel 1)
    - Chadwick, Major Frank, 1934 February 12 (Box 2, Folder 103, Reel 1)
    - Chałasinki, Jozef, 1937 December 14, 1938 July 8 (Box 2, Folder 104, Reel 1)
    - Champion, Pierre, 1932 January 26, February 5 (Box 2, Folder 105, Reel 1)
    - Chandra, Harish, 1933 May 31, June 12 (Box 2, Folder 106, Reel 1)
    - Character and Personality; C. E. Spearman, 1937 October 1 (Box 2, Folder 107, Reel 1)
    - Charak, Amy, 1936 September 22 (Box 2, Folder 108, Reel 1)
    - Charap, Leon, 1929 August 9 (Box 2, Folder 109, Reel 1)
    - Charles, Enid, 1932 June (Box 2, Folder 110, Reel 1)
    - Chiaromonte, Nicola, 1933 January-May (Box 2, Folder 111, Reel 1)
    - Christian, Bertram
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 113
    - Christian [Viktor?], 1932 July 14, August 15 (Box 2, Folder 112, Reel 1)
    - Christophers, Publishers; Bertram Christian, 1932, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 113, Reel 1)
    - Ciechomska, M., 1936 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 114, Reel 1)
    - Cincinnati Times-Star, Moses Strauss, managing editor, 1935 June 17, November 15 (Box 2, Folder 115, Reel 1)
    - Cipriano, Lidio, 1938 October 26 (Box 2, Folder 116, Reel 1)
    - City Literary Institute, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 117, Reel 1)
    - Clarke, Edith, 1930-1937 (Box 2, Folder 118, Reel 1)
    - Clifford, Miles, 1933 June 10, June 26 (Box 2, Folder 119, Reel 1)
    - Close, Sir Charles F., 1932 November 26, December 3 (Box 2, Folder 120, Reel 1)
    - Coleman, E. G., 1932 July 26 (Box 2, Folder 121, Reel 1)
    - Collège International de Cannes, Marcel Lob, 1933 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 122, Reel 1)
    - Collett, Enid M., 1933 June 30, July 8 (Box 2, Folder 123, Reel 1)
    - Colonial Office, London, re: training of Colonial Civil Servants in anthropology, 1931 September 8 (Box 2, Folder 124, Reel 1)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc.; Edward R. Murrow, 1936 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 125, Reel 1)
    - Comhaire-Sylvain, Suzanne, 1937 December 27, 1938 February 22 (Box 2, Folder 126, Reel 1)
    - Compagnia Italiana di Tourismo, London, 1936 February 17, February 22 (Box 2, Folder 127, Reel 1)
    - Connely, Willard
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 16
    - Cooke, C. C. R.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 285
    - Coon, Carleton and Mary G., 1936 November 8, December 10 (Box 2, Folder 128, Reel 1)
    - Copland, Douglas Berry, 1933 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 129, Reel 1)
    - Cordia, Reg, 1938 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 130, Reel 1)
    - Cosmopolitan Club, 1933 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 131, Reel 1)
    - Coulter, Charles W., 1935 May 1, May 18 (Box 2, Folder 132, Reel 1)
    - Creedy, L. A., 1933 January 26, February 2 (Box 2, Folder 133, Reel 1)
    - Crichton-Miller, Dr. and Mrs. [Hugh?], 1934 February 26, March 5, 19 (Box 2, Folder 134, Reel 1)
    - Crofton, Dr. Merwyn, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 135, Reel 1)
    - Crowdy, Elinor, 1932 July 28 (Box 2, Folder 136, Reel 1)
    - Crown, Dr. S., 1934 March 5, 6 (Box 2, Folder 137, Reel 1)
    - Cunard, Nancy, 1932-1938 (Box 2, Folder 138, Reel 1)
    - Dartington Hall, W. B. Curry, Headmaster, 1933 November 24, 1937 August 21 (Box 2, Folder 139, Reel 1)
    - Das, Tarak Chandra, 1936 April 22, 1938 July 11 (Box 2, Folder 140, Reel 1)
    - Dawson, Agnes, 1933 Oct, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 141, Reel 1)
    - Day, Edmund E.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 540
    - Decall, Rosa [governess], re: alien immigration and employment, 1932-1938 (Box 2, Folder 142, Reel 1)
    - DeGraft-Johnson, John Coleman, 1931-1933 (Box 2, Folder 143, Reel 1)
    - Walter de Gruyter and Co., 1931 November 26 (Box 2, Folder 144, Reel 1)
    - Dembowska, Alexandrine, 1930 August 23 (Box 2, Folder 145, Reel 1)
    - Dembowska, Zofja, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 146, Reel 1)
    - Dewey, John, 1935 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 147, Reel 1)
    - Dickinson, Frank, 1938 February 18, 27 (Box 2, Folder 148, Reel 1)
    - Dietrich, Ethel B., 1935 May 15, June 17 (Box 2, Folder 149, Reel 1)
    - Dobrzycki, St., 1916, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 150, Reel 1)
    - Doelberg, A., 1936 May 10 (Box 2, Folder 151, Reel 1)
    - The Dolmetsch Foundation, 1929, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 152, Reel 1)
    - Dombrowolski, Kazimierz, 1934 February 4 (Box 2, Folder 153, Reel 1)
    - Dougall, James W. C., Educational Advisor to the Missions in Kenya and Uganda, 1933 December 30, 1934 February 5 (Box 2, Folder 154, Reel 1)
    - Drew, Agnes, 1932 July 24, 1936 September 30 (Box 2, Folder 155, Reel 1)
    - Driberg, J. H., 1933 July 8 (Box 2, Folder 156, Reel 1)
    - Drzewiecka, Teodora, 1931 January 27 (Box 2, Folder 157, Reel 1)
    - Drzezińska, Anna, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 158, Reel 1)
    - Duhamel, Georges, 1938 June 21 (Box 2, Folder 159, Reel 1)
    - Dunham, Katherine, 1935 July 15, October 9 (Box 2, Folder 160, Reel 1)
    - The Eastern Province Herald, 1934 June 28 (Box 2, Folder 161, Reel 1)
    - Economic Reform Club, 1937 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 162, Reel 1)
    - Edmonds, Sophia, 1934 March 15, May 5 (Box 2, Folder 163, Reel 1)
    - Edwards, C. H., 1932 June 8, June 21 (Box 2, Folder 164, Reel 1)
    - Ehrenfels, Baron O. R., 1936, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 165, Reel 1)
    - Einaudi, Luigi, 1933 April-May (Box 2, Folder 166, Reel 1)
    - Elias, Norbert, 1938 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 167, Reel 1)
    - Elkan, Dr. Edward, 1937 April 13 (Box 2, Folder 168, Reel 1)
    - Ellis, Havelock, 1923-1936 (Box 2, Folder 169 - 170, Reel 1)
    - Emberismeret [Knowledge of Mankind, Hungarian Psychological Quarterly], 1935 September 20, 1936 March 26 (Box 2, Folder 171, Reel 1)
    - Embree, Edwin R., 1932-1936 (Box 2, Folder 172, Reel 1)
    - The Encyclopedia Britannica, 1928 June 18, 29 (Box 2, Folder 173, Reel 1)
    - Erdeljanović, Jovan, 1937 June-October (Box 2, Folder 174, Reel 1)
    - Estreicher, Stan., 1914, 1930-1938 (Box 2, Folder 175, Reel 1)
    - Eubank, Earle, 1935 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 176, Reel 1)
    - The Eugenics Society, 1932 October 8 (Box 2, Folder 177, Reel 1)
    - Eustis, Barbara, 1936 August-December (Box 2, Folder 178, Reel 1)
    - Evans-Pritchard, Edward Evan, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 179, Reel 1)
    - Faber and Faber, Publishers, Geoffrey Faber, 1932-1935 (Box 3, Folder 180, Reel 2)
    - F[alconer?], Hilda, 1916, undated (Box 3, Folder 181, Reel 2)
    - Fehling, A. W.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 541
    - Fei Hsiao-Tung, 1938 September 6, 10 (Box 3, Folder 182, Reel 2)
    - Fiedorowicz, G., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 183, Reel 2)
    - Field, G. C., 1932 May 24, August 28 (Box 3, Folder 184, Reel 2)
    - Field, M. J., 1933 January 14, February 20 (Box 3, Folder 185, Reel 2)
    - Field, Mrs. William B. Osgood [Alice Steelman Withrow], 1929 July 15 (Box 3, Folder 186, Reel 2)
    - Filipović, Milenko, 1938 March-September (Box 3, Folder 187, Reel 2)
    - Firth, Cedric H., undated (Box 3, Folder 188, Reel 2)
    - Firth, J. R., 1932-1933
    - Firth, Raymond W., 1931-1938 (Box 3, Folder 189, Reel 2)
    - Fischer, Adam, 1929 February 23 (Box 3, Folder 190, Reel 2)
    - Fischer, Eugen, 1938 August 20, September 11 (Box 3, Folder 191, Reel 2)
    - Fischer, Henri Theodore, 1938 May 27 (Box 3, Folder 192, Reel 2)
    - Fisher, Edjar J.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 290
    - Fisher, Ronald, 1935 March 18 (Box 3, Folder 193, Reel 2)
    - Fisher, Ruth Anna, 1932 October 21, 1933 February 15 (Box 3, Folder 194, Reel 2)
    - FitzGerald, C. P. [includes letter of recommendation and letter re: FitzGerald], 1938 September 20, 30 (Box 3, Folder 195, Reel 2)
    - Flügel, Ingeborg and John C., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 196, Reel 2)
    - Forde, Cyril Daryll, 1934 May 5, 8 (Box 3, Folder 197, Reel 2)
    - Forde, Robert, Jo and Mary Ellen, 1929 May 23 (Box 3, Folder 198, Reel 2)
    - Fortes, Meyer, 1932 June 21, 24, 1936 April 1 (Box 3, Folder 199, Reel 2)
    - Fortune, Reo F., Eileen, and Bart A., 1931-1938 (Box 3, Folder 200, Reel 2)
    - The Forum [letter of June 15, 1926 is incomplete], 1926 June 15, 1936 November 9 (Box 3, Folder 201, Reel 2)
    - Francis, E. Carey, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 202, Reel 2)
    - Frazer, Sir James G. and Lady Frazer, 1921-1938, undated (Box 3, Folder 203 - 204, Reel 2)
    - Frelinski, Stanislav, 1936 July 12 (Box 3, Folder 205, Reel 2)
    - Fremantle, Anne, 1934 February 14 (Box 3, Folder 206, Reel 2)
    - Freud, Anna, 1938 June 18 (Box 3, Folder 207, Reel 2)
    - Fry, Isabel, 1918 April 28 (Box 3, Folder 208, Reel 2)
    - Fuller, Clifford, 1935 July 11 (Box 3, Folder 209, Reel 2)
    - Fulton, G. R., 1932 June 23, 1934 March 5 (Box 3, Folder 210, Reel 2)
    - Fürstenberg, Baron Wilhelm von, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 211, Reel 2)
    - Gallas, Maryam, 1932 October 28, 1933 January 28 (Box 3, Folder 212, Reel 2)
    - Gallimard, Gaston
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 473
    - Gardiner, Alan Henderson, 1918 January 18 (Box 3, Folder 212A, Reel 2)
      See also: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 676
    - Gettell, Richard Glen, 1931 December 14, 1932 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 213, Reel 2)
    - Gibbons, Cecil W., 1932 September-November (Box 3, Folder 214, Reel 2)
    - Gidyński, K., 1931 January 16 (Box 3, Folder 215, Reel 2)
    - Gillon, André
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 474
    - Gilpin, Miss ______, 1933 July 11 (Box 3, Folder 216, Reel 2)
    - Gini, Corrado, 1930-1938 (Box 3, Folder 217, Reel 2)
    - Ginsberg, Morris, 1934 February 8, undated (Box 3, Folder 218, Reel 2)
    - Głos Współczesny, 1936 April 8 (Box 3, Folder 219, Reel 2)
    - Glover, Edward, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 220, Reel 2)
    - Głowna Księgarnia Wojskowa, 1935 March 25 (Box 3, Folder 221, Reel 2)
    - Gluckman, Max, 1936 June 29 (Box 3, Folder 222, Reel 2)
    - Gościcki, Stanisław, 1933 January 19 (Box 3, Folder 223, Reel 2)
    - Golding, Florence, 1914 September 13, undated (Box 3, Folder 224, Reel 2)
    - Gonzalez, Cecilia [fragment], undated (Box 3, Folder 225, Reel 2)
    - Gooch, George, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 226, Reel 2)
    - Goodfellow, D. M., 1933-1938 (Box 3, Folder 227, Reel 2)
    - Gould, F. J., 1933 May 24 (Box 3, Folder 228, Reel 2)
    - [Goyder?], Alexa, 1938 January 23 (Box 3, Folder 229, Reel 2)
    - Granquist, Hilma, 1932 February 21 (Box 3, Folder 230, Reel 2)
    - Grant-Duff, Ursula, 1931-1933 (Box 3, Folder 231, Reel 2)
    - Great Britain, Civil Services Commission, Leonard Blaikie, 1934, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 232, Reel 2)
    - Gregory, R. A.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 462
    - Grethlein and Co., 1930 June-August (Box 3, Folder 233, Reel 2)
    - Gross, Feliks, 1933-1938 (Box 3, Folder 234, Reel 2)
    - Gurewitsch, Sinowj, 1931 December 14, 1932 August 27 (Box 3, Folder 235, Reel 2)
    - Gurrey, P., 1937 December 1 (Box 3, Folder 236, Reel 2)
    - Haddon, A. C., 1924, 1934-1937 (Box 3, Folder 237, Reel 2)
    - Hadley, Helena, 1915 February 5, April 3 (Box 3, Folder 238, Reel 2)
    - Haensel, Paul, 1933 November 23 (Box 3, Folder 239, Reel 2)
    - Lord Hailey Survey
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 5
    - Haiman, Mieczyslaw, 1936 September 12, November 8 (Box 3, Folder 240, Reel 2)
    - Hall, H. U., 1933 June 8 (Box 3, Folder 241, Reel 2)
    - Hambly, Wilfred D., 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 242, Reel 2)
    - Hamilton, Jean, 1928 April 19 (Box 3, Folder 243, Reel 2)
    - Hammar, Gillis, 1938 July 20, 27 (Box 3, Folder 244, Reel 2)
    - Hancock, William ["Billy"], 1916-1920, undated (Box 3, Folder 245, Reel 2)
    - Handelsman, Marceli, 1934 Apr, undated (Box 3, Folder 246, Reel 2)
    - Hankins, Frank H., 1935 May 2, 21 (Box 3, Folder 247, Reel 2)
    - Hanline, Maurice A., 1928 July 27 (Box 3, Folder 248, Reel 2)
    - Harcourt, Brace and Company; Donald Brace, 1936 December 1, 11 (Box 3, Folder 249, Reel 2)
    - Harrasset, Albert, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 250, Reel 2)
    - Harris, I. M., 1936 (Box 3, Folder 251, Reel 2)
    - Harrison, Margaret Scott, 1938 August 1, September 10 (Box 3, Folder 252, Reel 2)
    - Harrisson, Tom H., 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 253, Reel 2)
    - Heard, Gerald, 1936 January 30 (Box 3, Folder 254, Reel 2)
    - Heaven, H. Stowe, 1936 June 23 (Box 3, Folder 255, Reel 2)
    - Herskovits, Melville and Frances, 1928-1936 (Box 4, Folder 256, Reel 2)
    - Herzberg, T. F., n.y. October 6 (Box 4, Folder 257, Reel 2)
    - Hijikata, Tatswzo, 1933 November 25, December 29 (Box 4, Folder 258, Reel 2)
    - C. L. Hirschfeld-Verlag, Leipzig, 1931 January 10, 1933 March 6 (Box 4, Folder 259, Reel 2)
    - Hodann, Max, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 260, Reel 2)
    - Hodgson, John, 1931 July 23 (Box 4, Folder 261, Reel 2)
    - Hoernlé, Agnes Winifred, 1935 July 2, 5 (Box 4, Folder 262, Reel 2)
    - Hofstra, Sjoerd, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 263, Reel 2)
    - Hogben, Lancelot, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 264, Reel 2)
    - Hogbin, Ian, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 265, Reel 2)
    - Hooper, Sidney E.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 76
    - Hooton, Earnest Albert, 1936 November 8, 1938 July 22 (Box 4, Folder 266, Reel 2)
    - [Hopkins?], Pryns, 1936 July 11 (Box 4, Folder 267, Reel 2)
    - Hopkinson, Thomas, n.y. July 16 (Box 4, Folder 268, Reel 2)
    - Hopkirk, D. S., 1938 March 16 (Box 4, Folder 269, Reel 2)
    - Horovitz, Dora, 1937 January 14, February 5 (Box 4, Folder 270, Reel 2)
    - Household Finance Company, 1936 October 1 (Box 4, Folder 271, Reel 2)
    - Howard, Evelyn E., 1932 May 27 (Box 4, Folder 272, Reel 2)
    - Howard, Elizabeth Fox, 1938 September 16, 29 (Box 4, Folder 273, Reel 2)
    - Howe, M. A. DeWolfe, 1936 July 27, December 22 (Box 4, Folder 274, Reel 2)
    - Howe, W. T. H.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 12
    - Howes, H. W., 1933 June 2, 1934 February 24, March 12 (Box 4, Folder 275, Reel 2)
    - Howland, George, 1933 March (Box 4, Folder 276, Reel 2)
    - Hudspeth, Doris, 1936 February 25 (Box 4, Folder 277, Reel 2)
    - Hughes, E. R., 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 278, Reel 2)
    - Huizinga, James, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 279, Reel 2)
    - Huizinga, Johan, 1926-1933 (Box 4, Folder 280, Reel 2)
    - Hunt, Atlee, Secretary of the Home and Territories Department of the Commonwealth of Australia [includes correspondence re: Malinowski], 1915-1918 (Box 4, Folder 281, Reel 2)
    - Huntington, Henry S., 1936 September 21 (Box 4, Folder 282, Reel 2)
    - Hurst, Dr. A. F., 1932 June 4 (Box 4, Folder 283, Reel 2)
    - Hussey, Eric R. J., 1932 February 18 (Box 4, Folder 284, Reel 2)
    - Huxley, Aldous [form letter], undated (Box 4, Folder 285, Reel 2)
    - Huxley, Julian, 1927 January 1, 1933 May 4, 26
    - Ibberson, Dora, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 286, Reel 2)
    - Imperial Bureau of Animal Genetics, University of Edinburgh, 1929 March 7 (Box 4, Folder 287, Reel 2)
    - The Incorporated Society of Authors, Playwrights and Composers, 1934 May 14 (Box 4, Folder 288, Reel 2)
    - Institute for the Scientific Treatment of Delinquency, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 289, Reel 2)
    - Institute of International Education, 1934-1938 (Box 4, Folder 290, Reel 2)
    - Institut Universaire des Hautes Etudes Internationales, 1938 February 1 (Box 4, Folder 291, Reel 2)
    - Instytut Gospodarstwa Społecznego, 1935 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 292, Reel 2)
    - Instytut Poperania Nauki, 1936 June 27 (Box 4, Folder 293, Reel 2)
    - International Congress of the History of Religions [VI, Brussels], Organizational Committee, 1935 April 25 (Box 4, Folder 294, Reel 2)
    - International Institute of African Languages and Cultures, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 295, Reel 2)
    - International Institute of Intellectual Cooperation, H. Bonnet, Director, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 296, Reel 2)
    - International Missionary Council, 1931 February 19 (Box 4, Folder 297, Reel 2)
    - Inter-State Commission, Commonwealth of Australia; A. G. Brown, Secretary, 1916 November 8 (Box 4, Folder 298, Reel 2)
    - Ischboldin, Boris, 1933-1936 (Box 4, Folder 299, Reel 2)
    - Iyer, L. K. Ananthakrishna, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 300, Reel 2)
    - Jabłoński, Stefan, 1927-1928 (Box 4, Folder 301, Reel 2)
    - Jabłoński, W. and Antonina, 1937 November 2 (Box 4, Folder 302, Reel 2)
    - Jackman, Harold, 1935 March 30 (Box 4, Folder 303, Reel 2)
    - Jacobi, Jolan
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 343
    - James, Edwin Oliver, 1932-1938 (Box 4, Folder 304, Reel 2)
    - Jarcho, Dr. Julius, 1934 January 2, 23 (Box 4, Folder 305, Reel 2)
    - Jelliffe, Belinda, n.y. September 18 (Box 4, Folder 306, Reel 2)
    - Jensen, Adolf, 1936 July 10, 1937 November 10 (Box 4, Folder 307, Reel 2)
    - Johannes, Frau _____, 1932 October 2 (Box 4, Folder 308, Reel 2)
    - John Hopkins University, Welsh Medical Library, 1935 January 9 (Box 4, Folder 309, Reel 2)
    - Johnson, C. B., 1916 December 31 (Box 4, Folder 310, Reel 2)
    - Johnson, Charles S., 1938 September 7, October 20 (Box 4, Folder 311, Reel 2)
    - Johnston, Alex, 1936 February 12 (Box 4, Folder 312, Reel 2)
    - Jonas, Mary C., 1918 October 28 (Box 4, Folder 313, Reel 2)
    - Jones, Ernest, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 314, Reel 2)
    - Jordan, Dr. Alfred Charles, 1932 October 14 (Box 4, Folder 315, Reel 2)
    - Journal of the Social Sciences ;D. N. Majumdar, Secretary, 1936 September 25 (Box 4, Folder 316, Reel 2)
    - The Journal Press, Provincetown, Mass.; Carl Murchison, Editor, 1936 September 25 (Box 4, Folder 317, Reel 2)
    - Joyce, Thomas A., 1934 May 9, 11 (Box 4, Folder 318, Reel 2)
    - Karasinski, Leon, 1929 April 6 (Box 4, Folder 319, Reel 3)
    - Karn, Dr., 1933 February 10 (Box 4, Folder 320, Reel 3)
    - Keith, Sir Arthur, 1928-1933 (Box 4, Folder 321, Reel 3)
    - Kelsen, Hans, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 322, Reel 3)
    - Kephart, C. I., 1935 November 4, 28 (Box 4, Folder 323, Reel 3)
    - Keppel, Frederick P.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 100
    - Kershaw, James A.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 460
    - Khuner, Hans, 1930 October 13 (Box 4, Folder 324, Reel 3)
    - Khuner, Paul, 1918, 1926-1932, undated (Box 4, Folder 325, Reel 3)
      See also: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 684
    - King, Copland, 1916 February 3 (Box 4, Folder 326, Reel 3)
    - Kirchoff, Paul, 1931-1934 (Box 4, Folder 327, Reel 3)
    - Kissling, W., 1931 (Box 4, Folder 328, Reel 3)
    - Kittredge, Eleanor, 1938 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 329, Reel 3)
    - Kittredge, Tracy B.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 542
    - Alfred A. Knopf, Ltd., 1928, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 330, Reel 3)
    - Kobylińska, Marja [cousin], 1929-1936 (Box 4, Folder 331, Reel 3)
    - Köhler, ______, 1933 November 19, 27 (Box 4, Folder 332, Reel 3)
    - Komierowski, A., 1933 November 10, December 11 (Box 4, Folder 333, Reel 3)
    - Korzybski, Alfred, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 334, Reel 3)
    - Kowalczyk, Edmund Louis, 1937 July 7 (Box 4, Folder 335, Reel 3)
    - Krajewski, Eugeniusz, 1936 October 15 (Box 4, Folder 336, Reel 3)
    - Kranold, Herman, 1934 March-May (Box 4, Folder 337, Reel 3)
    - Krause, Fritz, 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 338, Reel 3)
    - Kroeber, Alfred Louis, 1929 March 26 (Box 4, Folder 339, Reel 3)
    - Krueger, Felix, 1930 August 1 (Box 4, Folder 340, Reel 3)
    - Krzesinski, Andrzej, 1936 July 15 (Box 4, Folder 341, Reel 3)
    - Kubisz, Stanisław, 1931-1932 (Box 4, Folder 342, Reel 3)
    - Kulturbund; Jolan Jacobi, V. P., 1935 (Box 4, Folder 343, Reel 3)
    - Kuzytowics, Jerzy, 1937 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 344, Reel 3)
    - Kyrle, R. Money, 1936 April 22, May 15 (Box 4, Folder 345, Reel 3)
    - Labouret, Henri
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 295
    - Laforgue, René, 1933 April 14, May 3 (Box 4, Folder 346, Reel 3)
    - Lane, K. S., 1931-1937 (Box 4, Folder 347, Reel 3)
    - Lang-Kwang Hsu, 1938 June 3, September 27 (Box 4, Folder 348, Reel 3)
    - The Law Quarterly Review, A. L. Goodhart, Editor, 1936 November 26, December 9 (Box 4, Folder 349, Reel 3)
    - Lawrence, C. Margery, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 350, Reel 3)
    - League of Coloured Peoples, Harold A. Moody, 1933-1934 (Box 5, Folder 351, Reel 3)
    - League of Nations, Publications Department, 1932 December 13 (Box 5, Folder 352, Reel 3)
    - LeCoeur, Charles, 1933 July 2, 8 (Box 5, Folder 353, Reel 3)
    - Leeper, R. A., 1924 July 27 (Box 5, Folder 354, Reel 3)
    - Lees-Smith, H. B.
      See: Series I. Correspondence, 1869-1939 Folder 679
    - Lehmann, F. Rudolf, 1930-1938 (Box 5, Folder 355, Reel 3)
    - Lelek, Frant., 1934 February 14, March 5 (Box 5, Folder 356, Reel 3)
    - Le Souef, Ellie G., 1914 August 27 (Box 5, Folder 357, Reel 3)
    - Levinskaya, Maria [includes correspondence from Valetta Malinowska to Maria Levinskaya], 1933, 1938-1942 (Box 5, Folder 358, Reel 3)
    - Lewandowski, Herbert, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 359, Reel 3)
    - Leyder, Jean, 1933 July 5, 10 (Box 5, Folder 360, Reel 3)
    - Lightner, Grace H. [Mrs. Dean Howard Lightner], 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 361, Reel 3)